Guide to the Paul Ehrlich Papers SC0223
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- General Files and Correspondence, Series 1
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, T-W 1970 (Box 22, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, January 1970 (Box 22, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, February 1970 (Box 22, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, March 1970 (Box 22, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, April 1970 (Box 22, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, May-June 1970 (Box 22, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, July-October 1970 (Box 22, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, 197? (Box 22, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, A-B, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, C, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, D-F, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, G, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 97)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, H, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, I-J, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, K, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, L, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, M,N,O, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, P, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, R, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, S, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, Jan.- Feb., 1972 (Box 22, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, March - April 1972 (Box 22, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, May - June 1972 (Box 22, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, July - Aug. 1972 (Box 22, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, Sept.- Oct. 1972 (Box 22, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, Nov.- Dec. 1972 (Box 22, Folder 111)
  - Information for Persons interested in employment or education in environmental sciences (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Conservation List (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Genocide Statement (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - General Bibliography (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Herbicide References (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Pesticide Bibliography (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Pollution and the Environment (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Population Control (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Population Control and Genocide (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Population, Environment and Society (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Whales (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Academic Press (N.D.) (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Addison - Wesley Publishing Company [1964-1972] (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Allen Press [1965-1969] (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Allyn and Bacon, Inc. [1963] (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - A. Asher and Co. [1965] (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Ballinger Pub. - See Carl May in Correspondence Folder [Empty] (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Beacon Press [1972] (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Bobbs-Merrill [N.D.] (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - University of California Press [1967-1969] (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - University of Chicago Press [1964-1970] (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Change The Magazine of Learning [1977] (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - City Lights Bookstore [1969] (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Collier's Encyclopedia [1957-1970] (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Dickenson Publishing Co., Inc. [1967] (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Doubleday and Co. [1957-1970] (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - E.P. Dutton [1959-1973] (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Dover Publications [1962-66] (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Eerdmans Publishing Co. [1972] (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica Films [1963-1969] (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Fawcett World Library [1970] (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Free Press of Glencoe [1964-1965] (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Grosset and Dunlap, Inc. [1971] (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Hackett Publishers [1973] (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Harper and Brothers [1960-1971] (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Harper and Row [1969-1972] (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Harvard University Press [1968] (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston (General) [1966-1973] (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Harcourt, Brace, and World [1970] (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company [1968-1972] (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - John Hopkins Press [Empty] (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Indiana University Press [1968-1974] (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - William Kaufmann, Inc. [1973] (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Knopf [N.D.] (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Macmillan Company [1962-1972] (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - M.I.T. Press [1979] (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - The Natural History Press [1969] (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Natuur en Techniek [1969] (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - W.W. Worton and Co. [1968-1975] (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Oxford University Press [1970] (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Prentice-Hall [1960-1969] (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Ramparts [1969-1974] (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - W.B. Saunders Company [1961-1963] (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Science Research Associates, Inc. [1966-1970] (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Scott, Foresman and Company [1966] (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Silver Burdett Company [1966] (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Time-Life Books [1966-1969] (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Truex Press [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - John Wiley and Sons, Inc. [1968] (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Worth Publishers [1973-1975] (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Yale University Press [1970] (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - American Opinion [1971] (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - The Countryman (England) [1971-1972] (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Current [1972] (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Guardian (English - Anthony Tucker) [1972] (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Life [1970] (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Look [1970] (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Nola Express Publishers [1972] (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Saturday Evening Post [1972] (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Science Journal [1970] (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Science News / Science Service [1970] (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - True [1970-71] (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Washington Monthly [1970] (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - World Book Encyclopedia [1961-1971] (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - The Atlantic Monthly [1968] (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Canadian Nurse [1972] (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Commoner Debate -- Info on Double Publication (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Bioscience - AIBA Journal [1970-1975] (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Commoner Debate -- Publicity [1971-1972] (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Conservation [Empty] (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - "Controlling World Population" Consultant March 1969; Smits, Kline and French [1969] (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Chemistry [1965] (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Cross Currents "Pop, Explosion: Facts & Fiction" (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Der Spiegel [1968] (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Dialogue [1970] (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Encounter [1970] (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Family Weekly [1970] (Box 23, Folder 87)
  - Good Housekeeping [1970] (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Knight Magazine [1970] (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Liguorian [1970] (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - The Magazine [1970] (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Motive Magazine [1970] (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - OB Gym News [1969-1973] (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Per / Se [1968] (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Plain Truth [1969-1970] (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - Rotarian [1971] (Box 23, Folder 96)
  - Saturday Review [1972] (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - SR Drafts and Extras [1971] (Box 23, Folder 98)
  - "The Food from the Sea Myth", Saturday Review [1970] (Box 23, Folder 99)
  - Saturday Review - Correspondence [1970-1971] (Box 23, Folder 100)
  - Saturday Review - Reader Correspondence [1971] (Box 23, Folder 101)
  - SR Letter and Reply, (Energy Crisis). [Oct. 1971] (Box 23, Folder 102)
  - Scanlan's [1970] (Box 23, Folder 103)
  - Survival [1970] (Box 23, Folder 104)
  - Victor Bostrom Fund Report [1970] (Box 23, Folder 105)
  - Freshman Seminar (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Invitations Refused (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Honoraria Pending (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Hugh Moore Fund (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Key to Form Letters (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - PJG: Personal File (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Pending (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - People’s Lobby (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Pesticides (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Proposition 9 Endorsements (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Laurie Robinson (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Saturday Review (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Spring 1972 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Summer 1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Fall 1971 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Winter 1972 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Groups (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Vasectomies - Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - SSTs (Supersonic Transport) (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Pesticides - Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Historical Environmental Movement (Box 25)
  - Book: Opportunities in Environmental Careers (Box 25)
  - Declined Review Requests (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Invitations to Boards, Etc. - Declined (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Declined Misc. Requests and Invitations (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, O, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, R, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, General, Outgoing, 1972-73 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, General, Incoming, A-E, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, General, Incoming, F-G, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, General, Incoming, H-I, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, General, Incoming, J-L, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, General, Incoming, M, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, General, Incoming, O-P, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, General, Incoming, Q-W, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, Jan.- Feb. 1973 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, March - April, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, May - June, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, July - Aug., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, Sept.- Oct., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, Nov.- Dec., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, A-C, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, D-G, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, E-G, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, H-K, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, L-N, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, O-W, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, Jan.- Feb. 1974 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, March - April 1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, May 1974 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, July - August 1974 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, Sept.- Oct. 1974 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Outgoing, Nov.- Dec. 1974 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, A-B, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, C, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, D-G, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, H, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, I-J, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, K-L, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, M-P, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, R, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, S, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, T-Y, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, Jan.- March 1975 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, April - June 1975 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, July - Sept. 1975 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, Oct. - Dec. 1975 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, A-D, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, E-G, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, H, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, K, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, L-Q, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, R-Z, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, A-M, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, N-Z, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, A-W, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, A-Z, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Incoming, A-W, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence, General Public, Outgoing, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, Outgoing, N.D. (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Shirley Chisolm [1972] (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Harry Clench [1969] (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Cloud, Preston [1968-1969] (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Clowes, G. A. [1972] (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Joel [1970] (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Cooper, Ken [1971] (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Corbet, P. S. [1970-1974] (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Cornwell, G. [1973] (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Coulter, John [1973] (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Coulter, Malcolm [1970-1972] (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Norman Cousins [1971] (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Cross, Earle [1968-1971] (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Curtis, H. Pelham [Empty; see donor-file] (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - D, Misc. [1969-1975] (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Dahlberg, Kenneth [1974] (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Daleus, L.; Royal Swedish Acad. Sci. [1977] (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Dalrymple, Dana [1971-1975] (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Jim; Safari Air, Africa [1971] (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Day, M.F.; Australia [1971] (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Debell, Garnett [1970] (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Deeker, Dorothy [1972-1978] (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - De Lesse, H. (Paris; Butterflies) [1953-1957] (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - De Lisle, M. [1970] (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Druitt, W. [1974] (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Pugdale, Chester B. [1969-1977] (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Dybas, Henry [1969] (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - E, Misc. [1969-191970] (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Eaton III, Lafayette C. [1966-1969] (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Edsall, John T. [1972] (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Edson, Lee [1970] (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Edwards, Don [1974] (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Edwards, J. Gordon [1968-1971] (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Eflin, Dick [1972] (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Encel, Sol (Australia) [1972-1979] (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Enders, R. [1971] (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Enke, Stephen [1969-1970] (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Epel, D. [1969] (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Erickson, J. [1976] (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Ewell, Raymond [1968-1973] (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - F, Misc. [1970-1977] (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Faulkner, Peter T. [1974] (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Feeny, Paul [1971-1973] (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Figg-Hoblyn [1977] (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Fikes, Lee [1973] (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Forbes, W.T.M. [1957-1961] (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Ford, E.B. [1959-1975] (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Forrester, Jay [1972] (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Forrester, Theodore [1975] (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Fox, R.W. [1976-1978] (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Franklin, Betty; CAAP[1969-1970] (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Freedman, Jon; Crowding Studies; (See under Ford-Grants) [Empty] (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Fremlin, J.H. [1968-1973] (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Fromm, Erich [1976] (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Frost, David [1971-1972] (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - G., Misc. [1969-1978] (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - Goodall, Jane Van Lawick [1971-1974] (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - H., Misc. [1968-1979] (Box 28, Folder 57)
  - Hagen, Chet [1970] (Box 28, Folder 58)
  - Harris, Lola [1969] (Box 28, Folder 59)
  - Harrison, Gordon [1970-1972] (Box 28, Folder 60)
  - Hayden, Richard [1971-1972] (Box 28, Folder 61)
  - Hardwick, D.F. [1972] (Box 28, Folder 62)
  - Hasler, Arthur [1973] (Box 28, Folder 63)
  - Hedgpetn, Dr. Joel [1962-1971] (Box 28, Folder 64)
  - Hespenheide, H.A. [1973-1974] (Box 28, Folder 65)
  - Hickel, Walter J. [1968-1969] (Box 28, Folder 66)
  - Hessel, John [1967-1970] (Box 28, Folder 67)
  - Hunt, Peter S. [1970-71] (Box 28, Folder 68)
  - I., Misc. [1970-1975] (Box 28, Folder 69)
  - J., Misc. [1969-1977] (Box 28, Folder 70)
  - Jackson, Wes [1969-1972] (Box 28, Folder 71)
  - Johnson, Stanley P. (see also under Inten' / Planned Parenthood) [1973] (Box 28, Folder 72)
  - Johnson, Willard [1970-1974] (Box 28, Folder 73)
  - Jorden, Russel T. [1971-1972] (Box 28, Folder 74)
  - Justice, Keith [1965-1971] (Box 28, Folder 75)
  - K., Misc. [1967-1972] (Box 28, Folder 76)
  - Kalman, Summer [1967] (Box 28, Folder 77)
  - Klots, Alexander [1951-1971] (Box 28, Folder 78)
  - Kornberg, Arthur [1968] (Box 28, Folder 79)
  - Kurentzov, A.I. [1960-1971] (Box 28, Folder 80)
  - L. Misc. [1971-1979] (Box 28, Folder 81)
  - M., Misc. [1963-1978] (Box 28, Folder 82)
  - McCarthy, Eugene [1972] (Box 28, Folder 83)
  - McFarland, Noel [1959-1968] (Box 28, Folder 84)
  - McClintock, Mrs. Harvey [1968-1974] (Box 28, Folder 85)
  - McKinley, dan [1968-1976] (Box 28, Folder 86)
  - McNamara, Robert [1973] (Box 28, Folder 87)
  - Maequarie University; Australia (See Linacre in Correspondence File) [ Empty] (Box 28, Folder 88)
  - McReynolds, Maureen Sims (Ford Postdoctoral) [1968-1973] (Box 28, Folder 89)
  - Maey, Ralph (Box 28, Folder 90)
  - Matner, Bryant (Box 28, Folder 91)
  - Matnias, Boyd (Box 28, Folder 92)
  - Matnias, Charles (Box 28, Folder 93)
  - Mayer, Henry (Box 28, Folder 94)
  - Mayer, Ernst (Box 28, Folder 95)
  - Mead, Margaret (Box 28, Folder 96)
  - Paul K. Anderson (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Andrewartha, H. G. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Atherton, William (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Bakar, Gerson (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Bakus, Gerald - fish (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Ballantine, Ian (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Barrows, Perce S. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Baume, Peter (N. S. W.) (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Beer, Robert E. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Bengelsdorf, I. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Benoit, Emile (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Beregovoy, V. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Berelson, B. (see. Pop. Council) (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Berk, Joel S. (M.D.) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Bernard, Gary (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Bieber, K. (Senauke) (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Calabi, Paul (donors?) (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Canfield, Cass (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Cantor, Paul (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Castaneda, A. - Switzerland (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Catcheside, D. G. (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Caughley, Graeme - Australia (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Chambers, Ken (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Chase, Allen (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Chasteen, Ed (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Chen, P. C. (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Chitty, Dennis (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Chizea, Dora Obi. (See also African Environmental Assn.) (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Chizea, Dora Obi (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Incoming, 1967 (B-S) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Informative, Incoming, 1968 (A-Z) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Informative, Responses, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 A (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 B (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 C (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 G (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 H (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 (I-L) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 M (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 N (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 O (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 P (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 R (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 S (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 T (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Incoming, 1969 W-Z (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Responses, 1969 (Jan - March) (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Responses, 1969 (April - June) (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Responses, 1969 (July - Sept.) (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Outgoing, Oct. 1969 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Answers to Opinion, Nov 1969 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Information Seekers, Responses, Dec. 1969 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - [Musical Score: "Ecology’s Song"] (Box 35)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, A-B (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, C-D (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, E-H (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, I-K (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, L-M (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, N-P (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, Q-R (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, S (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Information Seekers, Incoming, 1970, T-Z (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses, Jan 1970 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses, Feb. 1970 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses, March 1970 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses, April 1970 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses, May 1970 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses,June 1970 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Information & Opinion Seekers, Responses, July 1970 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Misc. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - International Program for Population Analysis (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - International Nutrition & Development Foundation: Redwood City (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - International Studies Association (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Ecology (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Interdisciplinary Communications Program: Smithsonian Institution (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - NOAA: National Oceanography Assoc. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - NON: National Organization of Non-Parents (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - National Center for Health Statistics (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - National Wildlife Federation (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - National Comm. Supplies and Shortages, 1976-77 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Israel: Noise Pollution in, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Japanese Officials in Family Planning (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - League of Conservation Voters (Helen Edey) (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Water and Power Dept.: 1974-75 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - League of Women Voters of... (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - L.S.B. Leakey Foundation (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Marine Environmental Sciences Consortium: MESC (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - "Mothers of Twins" (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Mott Foundation (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - NEA (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - National Environment Foundation (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - National Intervenors (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - National Urban League (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - NECC: National Energy Conservation Challenge (Box 40, Folder 25)